Now the situation has changed.
Look at your right arm
and slowly move your right arm.
Notice what you see and feel.
As before, please raise your right hand
and make small regular movements
up and down, right and left, slowly.
Notice the movements of the body.
Now place your right hand on your left shoulder.
Observe.
Please raise your left hand
and make small regular movements
up and down, right and left, slowly.
Now place your left hand on your right shoulder.
Notice the movements of the body.
Now move your right hand to your lap
and then move your left hand to your lap.
Rest like this for a moment.
Where are you?
At the location of the body you see?
At the location from where you see?
Somewhere else?
Just notice and stay in this state.